A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1998-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1998-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
The Library of Virginia
51124
17.15 cu. ft. (49 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
These records are open for research but it may be necessary for an archivist to review Series II: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation files before they can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of the records can be made. Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years. Types of materials restricted include: social security numbers and confidential proprietary business records.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 8 January 2014 by the Office of Governor Robert F. McDonnell, Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1111 East Broad Street, 4th Floor, Richmond, Virginia, 23219.
Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties, compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now. The General Assembly in 1972 created six Secretariats positions initially. As government reorganized, that number fluctuated when government agencies expanded or consolidated. The office of the Secretary of Commerce and Resources was established in 1972 and was responsible for the areas of economic development and natural resources. In 1986 this secretariat was dissolved and split into two separate offices, the Secretary of Economic Development and the Secretary of Natural Resources. In 1993 the name of the office was changed from the Secretary of Economic Development to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. James S. Cheng served as Secretary of Commerce and Trade during Governor Robert F. McDonnell's administration (2010-2014).
The Secretary of Commerce and Trade is appointed by the governor and serves as a member of his cabinet. The Secretary of Commerce and Trade's chief responsibility is to manage the direction of several state agencies that are concerned with the development of commerce and economic development throughout the Commonwealth. Some of the agencies reporting to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade include: Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services; Department of Economic Development; Department of Labor and Industry; Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy; Virginia Employment Commission; Virginia Housing Development Authority; Department of Professional and Occupational Regulations; Department of Housing and Community Development; Milk Commission; Department of Minority Business Enterprise; Department of Forestry; Virginia Port Authority; Virginia Racing Commission; and Virginia Resource Authority.
Scope and Content
Records, 1998-2014 (bulk 2010-2013), of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade during the administration of Governor Robert F. McDonnell. The collection is housed in 49 boxes and includes agendas, briefings, brochures, calendars, clippings, correspondence, financial statements, itineraries, memorandum, newsletters, notes, programs, publications, reports, and other documents.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into six series:
Series I: Appointment calendars, 2010-2013
Series II: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2009-2013
Series III: Subject files, 1998-2013
Series IV: Development Projects and Initiatives files, 2009-2013
Series V: Governor's Opportunity Fund files, 2008-2013
Contents List
- Series I: Appointment calendars, 2010-2013., Extent: 2.35 cu. ft. (7 boxes) (Box 1-7)
  Series I: Appointment calendars, 2010-2013, is housed in seven boxes and arranged chronologically. This series includes the appointment calendars of Secretary James S. Cheng, 2010-2013, Deputy Secretary Carrie Roth, 2010, and Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010. Included within the calendars are agendas, correspondence, invitations, memorandum, notes, and reports regarding specific appointments.
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 March 1-9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 March 10-19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 March 22-31 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 April 1-14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 April 15-29 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 May 3-7 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 May 8-13 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 May 17-21 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 May 26-27 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 June 1-27 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 July 6-26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 July 27-August 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2010 August 3-September 13 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, Misc., 2011 March-2012 January (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 March 21 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 July 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 August-December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2011 November 2-3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 January (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 February (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 March (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 April (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 April 24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 May (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 June (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 July (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 July (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 August (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 September (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 October (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 November (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2012 December 19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 January (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 February (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 March (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 April (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 May (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 June (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 July (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 August (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 September (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Appointment calendar, Secretary Jim Cheng, 2013 December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Deputy Secretary Carrie Roth, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010 February 2-25 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Appointment calendar, Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010 March 1-April 4 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Appointment calendar, Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010 April 5-May 18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Appointment calendar, Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010 May 19-June 8 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Appointment calendar, Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010 June 9-July 27 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendar, Senior Economic Advisor Robert "Bob" Sledd, 2010 August 16-17 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Series II: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2009-2013., Extent: 4.1 cu. ft. (12 boxes) (Box 8-19)
  Series II: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation is housed in twelve boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. Includes correspondence from various agencies under the Secretary, such as the Virginia Employment Commission (VEC); Virginia Tourism Corporation (VTC); Department of Housing and Community Development (DHCD); Virginia Resources Authority (VRA); Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy (DMME); Virginia Housing Development Authority (VHDA); and Virginia Economic Development Partnership (VEDP). Also included is incoming and outgoing correspondence of Secretary Cheng and correspondence from Governor McDonnell. This series also includes decision tracking sheets and status updates.
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2010 January-February (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2010 February-March (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2010 March (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2010 March-April (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2010 April (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2010 (Misc.)-2011 March (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2011 April-July (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2011 August-2012 January (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, Dept. Mines, Minerals, and Energy, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, Dept. Mines, Minerals, and Energy, 2010 January-March (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Assigned State Agencies, Dept. Mines, Minerals, and Energy, 2010 March-April (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010 February-June (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010 July-October (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010 October-December (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 January-February (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 March-June (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 June (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 July-September (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 September-December (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 December (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2011 November-2012 April (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2012 April-August (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2012 September-December (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2010 January-June (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2010 July-August (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2010 September-December (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2010 December-2011 April (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2011 May-August (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2011 September-December (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2012 January-May (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Incoming, 2012 June-December (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Outgoing, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Outgoing, 2011 January-June (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Outgoing, 2011 July-August (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Outgoing, 2011 September-December (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Outgoing, 2011 December-2012 December (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Secretary James S. Cheng, Outgoing, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Community Relations Issues, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Appointment Process to Boards and Commissions, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Decisions, 2010 November-December (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Decisions, 2010 December-2011 January (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Decisions, 2011 January-February (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Decisions, 2011 February (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Decisions, 2011 June (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Decisions, 2011 June-September (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Decisions, 2011 December-2012 June (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Decision Tracking Sheet, 2010 February-May (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Decision Tracking Sheet, 2010 June-September (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Decision Tracking Sheet, 2010 September-December (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Events, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Events, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Events, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Events, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 January-February (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 March (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 April-May (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 June (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 June-July (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 August-September (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 September-November (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Gold Sheets, 2011 November-December (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Gold Sheets, 2012 January-February (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gold Sheets, 2012 February (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Gold Sheets, 2012 February-March (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Status Updates, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Status Updates, 2010-2011 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Status Updates, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Status Updates, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Series III: Subject files, 1998-2013., Extent: 6.65 cu. ft. (19 boxes) (Box 20-38)
  Series III: Subject files is housed in nineteen boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series includes correspondence, memorandum, minutes, newsletters, notes, programs, publications, reports, and surveys. Subjects include: budget, campus safety, economic development, Fort Monroe Authority, Governor's Commission on Economic and Job Creation, higher education, housing and homelessness, off shore wind and Outer Continental Shelf oil leasing, tax incentives, Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund, uranium mining, and Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, among others.
  - Asbestos, Lead, Mold, and Home Inspectors, Virginia Board for, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Accountancy, Virginia Board of, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Boards, Misc. list, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Business Assistance, Virginia Dept. of, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Call sheets, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
  - Certificates, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cemetery Board, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Clean Energy Manufacturing Incentive grant, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - College Campus Safety Board, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Military and National Security Facilities, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Research Commercialization Fund, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, Agency briefing documents, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 6-8)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, Report on Policy Transition Committee, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, Strategic plans, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, Strategic plan, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, Strategic plan, 2010-2011 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Community Action Agencies, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 2009-2011 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Misc., 2011-2013 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Cyber Security Initiative, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - EB-5 Virginia, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Economic Crisis Task Force, undate (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Historic preservation manual and design standards, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2010 March 25 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2010 May 20 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2010 June 24 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2010 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2010 October 21 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Financial reports, 2011 June (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 July 7 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 July 11 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 August 8 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 August 18 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 September 29 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 October 21 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2011 December 12 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2012 March 20 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2012 July 26 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2012 November 7 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2012 December 13 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2013 May 23 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Fort Monroe Authority, Meeting agenda and minutes, 2013 October 24 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - FOIA, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Geology, Board for, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Government Reform and Reinstructing Commission, Briefing, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Government Reform and Reinstructing Commission, Surveys, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Public meetings, 2010 July-September (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Final report, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, Final reports, Sub-groups, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Commission on Higher Education Reform, Innovation, and Investment, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Commission on Higher Education Reform, Innovation, and Investment, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Energy Conference, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Forum on Education and Workforce Training Planning Committee, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Modeling and Simulation Advisory Council, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Motion Picture Opportunity Fund, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Opportunity Fund Distressed Communities in Virginia, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Red Carpet Tour (SW Va.), 2011 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Student Entreprenourship Competition, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Workforce Development Task Force, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Health, Virginia Dept. of, Drywall Task Force, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Health, Virginia Dept. of, Drywall Task Force, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - House Bill 2324 / Senate Bill 1485, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Housing and Community Development, Virginia Dept. of, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Housing and Community Development, Virginia Dept. of, 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Housing and Community Development, Virginia Dept. of, Proposed regulations, 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Housing Development Authority, Virginia, Reports, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Housing Development Authority, Virginia, Reports, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Housing Development Authority, Virginia, Reports, 2011-2013 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hydraulic fracturing, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Interstate Mining Compact Commission, Annual report, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - IQ System and CR responsiveness, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Irish Ambassador reception, 2010 June 5 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - JLARC, Reducing Veteran Homelessness in Virginia, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Legal filings, 2012-2013 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
  - Local Mandates Task Force, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Lynchburg Regional Chamber, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Manufacturing Development Commission, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Manufacturing Development Commission, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, 2011-2012 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, Notes, 2010-2011 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum, 2010 January-February (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum, 2010 March-August (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Collaborative Green Consortium, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Misc., 2010-2013 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Misc., 2010-2013 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Misclassification, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Office of Economic Adjustment Grant, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Outer Continental Shelf Oil and Gas Leasing Program, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Professional and Occupation Regulation, Dept. of, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Project Trace, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Race to the Top, Earl learning, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Senate Bills, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Single Sales Factor Apportionment, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Southern Governor's Association, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - State Inspector General, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Status updates, 2011-2012 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Tax incentives, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Tour of Virginia's Great Southwest, 2010 June (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Trade mission to Israel and India, 2011 November (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), 2010-2011 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), 2011 August (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), Meeting minutes, 2011 September 30 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), Meeting minutes,, 2012 February 23 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), Meeting minutes,, 2012 May 5 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), Meeting minutes,, 2012 November 19 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), Meeting minutes,, 2013 May 31 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF), Meeting minutes,, 2013 June 28 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Unanswered prayers reception, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - UCI World Road Cycling Championship, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Uranium mining, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 1)